eguide.com.sg 2017-06-06

# eGuide Business Directory - Terms & Conditions

###  Can’t find an answer to your question or concerns? Contact us, we will respond. 

Online Privacy Policy   
Catch 

This privacy policy applies to all personal information collected by Catch via the internet. 

Catch recognises the importance of your privacy, and that you have a right to control how your personal information is collected and used. We know that providing personal information is an act of trust and we take that seriously. Unless you directly give us consent to do otherwise, Catch will only collect and use your personal information as set out below. 

#### Collection of information

The four main ways we collect personal information about you are: 

  * when information about you is posted on a Catch website, either by you or by a third party; 
  * when you log into or access a Catch website or otherwise submit personal information to Catch; 
  * when you use a Catch website, in which case our system automatically collects information relating to your visit to that website, such as your IP address; and 
  * through the operation of CatchBot, Catch's web crawler (described in more detail below). 

The type of information that we collect from you may include the following: your name, phone number, address, email address, company position/title, credit card details, IP address, cookies, personal information that you include in your business listing or personal information that you email/send using email functionality on the Eguide Website. 

#### Our use of cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record keeping purposes. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. Catch uses cookies to make your use of our website and services as convenient as possible. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's browser. Cookies are useful to estimate our number of users and determine overall traffic patterns through our website. 

If you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to refuse cookies. This may mean you will not be able to take full advantage of Catch's services. 

_Google cookies_

Catch uses Google to serve advertisements when you visit a Catch website. Google may use cookies in relation to your visits to Catch websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services which may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about Google not using cookies in this way, [click here](http://www.google.sg/privacy_ads.html). 

#### Using and disclosing your personal information

Our purpose in collecting information about you is to: 

  * provide you with a better service experience with content and advertising that is more relevant to your interests; and 
  * create a business information database for use as part of Catch's online business. Whilst Catch's business information database is designed to operate as a business directory (not a directory of individuals) it is possible that personal information may become included in the business information database. 

Catch will not use or disclose any information about you without your consent, unless: 

  * the use or disclosure is for one of the purposes described above or otherwise permitted by this policy; 
  * it is required or permitted by law (including by relevant privacy laws); 
  * we believe it necessary to provide you with a service which you have requested; 
  * to protect the rights, property or personal safety of another Catch website user, any member of the public or Catch; or 
  * any of the assets and/or operations of Catch are being transferred to another party. 

If you do not provide requested information, Catch may not be able to provide you with access to or full use of sections of the Catch website. 

#### Disclosing information

Sometimes, the activities described above require us to share your personal information with other organisations. The types of situations in which Catch usually discloses personal information, and the types of organisations to which such disclosure is usually made, include the following: 

  * The business information database is available via the internet to any member of the public. It is also disclosed in its entirety to Catch's related entities and to other entities with whom Catch has a business relationship, as part of Catch's online business. 
  * Catch discloses personal information to its service providers, advisers and other entities with whom Catch has a business relationship, in the course of operating the Catch websites and Catch online business and in the course of delivering the Catch services. 

#### Marketing

In seeking to give you the most worthwhile experience of our websites possible, Catch may use your personal information to send you information and product updates about Catch websites and services, or other products and services, or to permit other parties to send other information about products or services which may be of interest to you. 

We may contact you at any email or other address or contact point which we have collected or obtained in order to: 

  * contact you about your business listing on a Catch website; 
  * provide you with updated information about Catch websites; or 
  * provide you with other information about other products or services which you may enjoy. 

If you are receiving promotional information from Catch and do not wish to receive this information any longer, you may remove your name from our list by contacting the Catch Privacy Officer at [legal@eguide.com.sg](mailto:legal@eguide.com.sg) and asking to be removed from our mailing list. Please allow 28 days for this request to be processed. 

#### Access to the information we hold

You can request access to the personal information we hold about you by making a request to the Catch Privacy Officer via [legal@eguide.com.sg](mailto:legal@eguide.com.sg). We will provide you with access unless we are legally authorised not to do so. 

#### Changing and deleting the information we have about you

If at any time you wish to change personal information that is inaccurate or out of date, please contact us by emailing our Catch Privacy Officer at [legal@eguide.com.sg](mailto:legal@eguide.com.sg) If you wish to have your personal information deleted, please let us know in the same manner as referred to above. 

We will take all reasonable steps to change or delete information in response to such a request. If there is a reason that we cannot make that change or deletion, we will inform you of that reason. 

#### Storage and security of your personal information

Catch will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. You should note that the internet is not a secure method of transmitting information and, as such, we are not responsible for the security of any information sent or received over the internet. 

Please note that Catch may use overseas facilities including but not limited to in the US and Australia, to store, process or back up its information. As a result, we may transfer your personal information to our overseas facilities. However, this does not change our commitment to keep your information secure. 

#### Third party websites

Catch websites contain links to websites that are not operated by Catch and the contact details for many businesses not operated by Catch. These linked sites and listed businesses are not under the control of Catch, and we are not responsible for the conduct of those businesses. Before disclosing your personal information on any other website or to any other company, we advise you to examine the Terms and Conditions / Privacy Policy of those organisations. 

#### CatchBot

CatchBot is the web crawler for Catch. CatchBot investigates websites for publicly available information about companies. CatchBot is not designed to access or index any personal or other information about individuals. However, if any personal information is collected inadvertently through the use of CatchBot, that personal information will be held in accordance with this Privacy Policy. More information about CatchBot is available at [www.catchbot.com](http://www.catchbot.com/). 

#### Privacy inquiries

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or how Catch deals with your personal information you can contact: 

Catch Privacy Officer   

Catch is the online division of Cirrus Media Pty Limited (Australia). All references to Catch in this Privacy Policy should therefore be read as references to Cirrus Media Pty Limited (ABN 80 132 719 861), an Australian company. 

#### Future changes

Our commitment to being a leading provider of online business directory services means that our business will continue to evolve as we introduce new services and features. Because of this, from time to time, our policies will be reviewed and may be revised. Catch reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time and notify you by posting an updated version on each Catch website. The amended Privacy Policy will apply between us whether or not we have given you specific notice of any change. 

* * *
